export default [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "What is the name of an animal that eats meat?",
        answer: "carnivore",
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "What is the name of an animal that eats vegetables?",
        answer: "herbivore",
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "What is the process plants undergo to convert light energy into chemical energy?",
        answer: "photosynthesis",
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "What is the powerhouse of the cell?",
        answer: "mitochondria",
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Organisms that make there own food compounds using the Sun's energy are called?",
        answer: "producers",
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        question: "A type of symbiotic relationship where all species involved benefit from their interactions are called?",
        answer: "mutualism",
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "What component main component makes up the Earth's atmosphere?",
        answer: "nitrogen",
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "What is the basic Unit of a living organism?",
        answer: "cell",
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "What is the process of molecules moving from an area of high concentration to low concentration?",
        answer: "diffusion",
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Organisms that break down waste from plants/animals and their dead remains are called?",
        answer: "decomposers",
    }

]